[Music]
[音乐]
帕卡诺书之后，最后一本
[Music]
after the pacano books which the last
一个是在1949年，
爸爸的动作以及下一个动作
after the pacano books which the last
one was in 1949 there was quite a gap in
我得证明你是从1950年开始
被罗兰称为美女与野兽
one was in 1949 there was quite a gap in
much Papa action and the next one that
PIM非常漂亮的小书
简单的纸张工程，一切都基于
much Papa action and the next one that
I've got to show you is from 1950 this
关于并行故障的教程
六，如果我们只看它就可以了
I've got to show you is from 1950 this
is called Beauty and the Beast by Roland
看到它有这六个面包
六个场景，每个场景由四个组成
is called Beauty and the Beast by Roland
PIM beautiful little book very very
中间有折叠的床单
我们有这是前一个然后一个
PIM beautiful little book very very
simple paper engineering it's all based
再往后一点一点
最后一个，如果我们再看一下，我会
simple paper engineering it's all based
on parallel faults which are tutorial
只是把它打开就可以了
环顾四周，看看我到底是什么
on parallel faults which are tutorial
six if we just look at it end on you can
真的很喜欢这样
如果我们创造令人难以置信的视角
six if we just look at it end on you can
see it has these six breads
这样看我就去
通过他们所有的六个，你会看到
see it has these six breads
six scenes each of which is made of four
床单如何被切掉
聪明的方法来给一个真正的
six scenes each of which is made of four
sheets with a fold in the middle so
每个场景都有非凡的深度感
我有不同的语气
sheets with a fold in the middle so
we've got this is the front one then one
只是认为这是一个非常美丽的作品
接下来的两本书来自1960年
we've got this is the front one then one
a bit further back third one and the
我不知道造纸工程师是谁
这些是1960年，它们都是用
a bit further back third one and the
final one and if we then look at it I'll
教程12中的浮动平面
和平行四边形教程5我只是
final one and if we then look at it I'll
just tie it open and then we can go
认为这些插图是
美丽，他们每个都有两个点差
just tie it open and then we can go
around and look at it simply what I
在这里，如果我们看看它到底
您可以看到浮动平面机制
around and look at it simply what I
really like about this is the way
中间有平行折叠
那么平行四边形就出来了
really like about this is the way
incredible perspective is created if we
从
他们有这些疯狂的小拉力
incredible perspective is created if we
look at it like this I'll just go
标签非常粗糙的机制，
效果非常令人愉悦
look at it like this I'll just go
through all six of them and you'll see
本书的第一个，然后
在这种情况下，其他在后面传播
through all six of them and you'll see
how the sheets are cut away in very
好在这里的顶部，海洋弹出
从罐子里拿出另一个
how the sheets are cut away in very
clever ways to give a really
我得到的这个系列是阿拉丁
他的魔灯
clever ways to give a really
extraordinary sense of depth each scene
从1960年开始就一直浮动
平面和平行四边形漂亮
extraordinary sense of depth each scene
has a different sort of tone to it I
艺术品在这里，它带来了
这个怪物的采访所以下一步
has a different sort of tone to it I
just think it's a really beautiful piece
向前是Wojtek cabassa在
捷克斯洛伐克，他做了两种类型的书
just think it's a really beautiful piece
of work the next two books are from 1960
他做了这些panis Copic模型，
这些孩子的故事也是这样
of work the next two books are from 1960
I don't know who the paper engineer was
我会穿过这三个潘尼斯
Copic首先建模这个是
I don't know who the paper engineer was
these are 1960 they're all made with
克里斯托弗·哥伦布1960年在这里
这种传播是绝对经典的
these are 1960 they're all made with
floating planes which are tutorial 12
克里斯托弗·哥伦布的船，如果我们
看一下机制
floating planes which are tutorial 12
and parallelograms tutorial 5 I just
这些是曲折褶皱
教程20这是一个锯齿形的折痕
and parallelograms tutorial 5 I just
think the illustration in these is
另一个锯齿形折叠大多数教程20和
再次，如果我们看这是一个
think the illustration in these is
beautiful they've got two spreads each
锯齿形折叠并添加平行四边形
过去的教程六全部组合在一起
beautiful they've got two spreads each
here it is and if we look at it end on
带插槽
那是教程11的可爱片段
here it is and if we look at it end on
you can see the floating plane mechanism
设计这个，我想要的第二个
告诉你是1961年，这叫做
you can see the floating plane mechanism
with the parallel fold in the middle and
城堡锦标赛
Wojtek电容器又在这里
with the parallel fold in the middle and
then the parallelogram is coming out
惊人的弹出式城堡基本上是主要的
机制是V形折叠，所以这是一个
then the parallelogram is coming out
from
v形折叠为其余部分提供动力
很多，我喜欢插图
from
and they have these crazy little pull
显示实际上是
城堡，尽管没什么
and they have these crazy little pull
tabs very crude mechanisms that the the
像前面一样的全彩色
只是在整个设计中添加了一些东西
tabs very crude mechanisms that the the
effects are very pleasing that's the
如果我们看完它，你可以看到
这是第二个错误，这是一个
effects are very pleasing that's the
first one in this book and then the
平行四边形连接两个圆
并仔细看所有这些
first one in this book and then the
other spread at the back in this case
是不对称的v形折叠
这两个部分在这里和
other spread at the back in this case
well the top here and the Seas pop up
这是不对称的
这些的肉丸教程是
well the top here and the Seas pop up
out of the jars and the other one in
只是非常简单的一点
这些平面上出现平行四边形
out of the jars and the other one in
this series that I've got is Aladdin and
这里的平行四边形教程五
所以我们有了这些小动作
this series that I've got is Aladdin and
his magic lamp
这里的机制非常简单非常基本
而且另一边也一样
his magic lamp
from 1960 it's the same it's floating
然后这最后一点是
对称平行折叠教程六和
from 1960 it's the same it's floating
planes and parallelograms beautiful
最后一位是马可波罗
1962年，我们将这一门打开了
planes and parallelograms beautiful
artwork here's the tab and it brings
非凡的弹出窗口，这真的真的
这些可爱的弹出式设计
artwork here's the tab and it brings
this monster interview so the next step
背部
这些是曲折褶皱，它们是
this monster interview so the next step
forward was Wojtek cabassa working in in
根据我在解释中的修改
本教程本教程20这是一个
forward was Wojtek cabassa working in in
czechoslovakia he did two types of books
基本V折这里教程2切入
拱形的形式
czechoslovakia he did two types of books
he did these panis Copic models and he
教程34这是额外的折痕
那是教程7，有一个平行的
he did these panis Copic models and he
also did these children's stories so
折叠这片向前突出
那是教程6，还有
also did these children's stories so
I'll just run through these three panis
柜台折成这样一块
背面是对折
I'll just run through these three panis
Copic models first this one is
那是教程22在一起
插槽少，教程11高度
Copic models first this one is
Christopher Columbus 1960 so here it is
弹出设计有点复杂，但是
现在我们只有非常惊人的价差
Christopher Columbus 1960 so here it is
and this spread is an absolute classic
看那里的电容器童话故事
实际上是几十个
and this spread is an absolute classic
Christopher Columbus's ship and if we
1961年以来的睡美人
所有这些书中的机制都是
Christopher Columbus's ship and if we
look at the mechanisms
反折教程22他们通常
有一些有趣的小东西
look at the mechanisms
these are zigzag folds which are
运动部件非常非常简单
在这里，我们有王子变成
these are zigzag folds which are
tutorial 20 here's a zigzag fold is
女巫，如果我们打开它一样
我们有这些窗口或空的东西
tutorial 20 here's a zigzag fold is
another zigzag fold most tutorial 20 and
通过拉动条带，我们得到了这些
三个恩典或其他恩典
another zigzag fold most tutorial 20 and
again if we look at this this is a
全部反折，因此当页面是
其他一切都变得平坦了
again if we look at this this is a
zigzag fold with added parallelograms
如果您全都砍掉一张卡
看着它结束，你会看到
zigzag fold with added parallelograms
past tutorial six all fitted together
整个事情实际上是
手风琴只是一长条
past tutorial six all fitted together
with slots
所有这些非常聪明的柜台卡
褶皱切出给你
with slots
that's tutorial 11 lovely piece of
普通的平行四边形成角度的褶皱和
我们只是穿过这是城堡
that's tutorial 11 lovely piece of
design this and the second one I'd like
这有另一个你可以拉
看看发生了什么，所以我喜欢这样
design this and the second one I'd like
to show you is 1961 this is called the
这个彩色玻璃窗变成一个
猫头鹰，我们有这个，在这里变成一个
to show you is 1961 this is called the
castle tournament
彩色玻璃窗非常简单
拉条，这里我们还有另一个
castle tournament
Wojtek capacitor again and here it is
我认为没有什么可动的
在那，然后这个我不认为
Wojtek capacitor again and here it is
amazing pop-up castle basically the main
有什么可以继续前进的
这些那里有这些
amazing pop-up castle basically the main
mechanism is a v-fold so this this is a
摇头很好，没有拉力
剥离去做，你只需要去做
mechanism is a v-fold so this this is a
v-fold which is powering the rest of it
用手指他们都在点头
睡觉的最后一个传播是
v-fold which is powering the rest of it
a lot of it I like the illustration
一个，你实际上可以拉标签
王子穿过拱门来到
a lot of it I like the illustration
showing actually the inside of the
给她一个案例，这是睡美人
从1961年开始，这些非常早期的电容器
showing actually the inside of the
castle even though it's nothing
后来有八点差
他们减少到六个，所以我只给你看一个
castle even though it's nothing
full-color like the front it's still
其他几个是法语版本
小火车
full-color like the front it's still
just adds something to the whole design
这是1973年全部用反折制成
与上一本书的教程相同22
just adds something to the whole design
if we look at it end on you can see this
在这个每个传播都有一些真正
简单的运动，所以在这个
if we look at it end on you can see this
is a second be fault here and this is a
你知道火车做一些有趣的事
现在移动，这是一个非常不错的
is a second be fault here and this is a
parallelogram joining the two come round
你拉这些小老鼠，我们得到一些
好玩
parallelogram joining the two come round
and look at it all and these bits these
那里再次打鼓的塑料动作
实际的机制真的很简单
and look at it all and these bits these
are asymmetric v-folds that are holding
所以你实际上必须持有它
是的，否则会开始出错，但是
are asymmetric v-folds that are holding
the these two pieces this piece here and
我只是觉得这很有趣
他鼓，下一个传播这个
the these two pieces this piece here and
this piece here these are asymmetric
是的，没有什么可动的
这些只是悬而未决的
this piece here these are asymmetric
meatballs tutorial for these these are
一个是风车又是你
知道没有拉条或其他任何东西
meatballs tutorial for these these are
just very straightforward little
只要你可以转弯
要和最后一个，所以这是这个
just very straightforward little
parallelograms coming off these planes
从1979年开始，直到现在
电容器还是所有相同的技术
parallelograms coming off these planes
here the parallelograms a tutorial five
用对折制成
月亮火箭这是1986年，这是
here the parallelograms a tutorial five
so we've got these little moving
您按下的第一个它启动
火箭二号这是
so we've got these little moving
mechanisms here very simple very basic
指南27集线器和枢轴
整个系列的事情在这里改变
mechanisms here very simple very basic
and we've got the same on the other side
你已经在计算机上阅读了
改变你已经改变了这个表盘
and we've got the same on the other side
and then this this final bit that's a
而且你周围还有地方
世界，你已经有了巴黎莫斯科北京
and then this this final bit that's a
symmetric parallel fold tutorial six and
科隆和意大利纽约
当您采取这种传播措施时，
symmetric parallel fold tutorial six and
the last one this is Marco Polo from
上下拉动他的头
手臂上的机器人移动漂亮的克伦克
the last one this is Marco Polo from
1962 and we open this one up quite an
真的，但这就是你所追求的
将视图移出舷窗
1962 and we open this one up quite an
extraordinary pop-up this really really
所有这些动作都很有趣
关于它们是很粗糙的纸
extraordinary pop-up this really really
lovely piece of pop-up design these at
机械师，这是由插槽
那是教程11，其余的就是
lovely piece of pop-up design these at
the back
柜台折页教程22
这是你想做的下一个价差
the back
these are zigzag folds they're a
火箭走了，你就把它举起来
没有什么聪明的
these are zigzag folds they're a
modification from what I explained in
这只是一个简单的上下
那么我们有这个红色
modification from what I explained in
the tutorial this tutorial 20 this is a
这是最后的传播只是拉这些
一遍又一遍
the tutorial this tutorial 20 this is a
basic V fold here tutorial 2 it's cut in
所以它们只是非常简单的玩具
真的这些是持有这个的插槽
basic V fold here tutorial 2 it's cut in
the form of an arch which is hovered in
那是教程11，其余的就是
反折教程22，如果你做
the form of an arch which is hovered in
tutorials 34 this is extra creases
书本整平
都是由一个巨大的
tutorials 34 this is extra creases
that's tutorial 7 there's a parallel
这些柜台很多的六角琴
折入其中，这是电容器
that's tutorial 7 there's a parallel
fold this piece jutting forward
在捷克斯洛伐克工作，他
启发沃尔多在加利福尼亚狩猎
fold this piece jutting forward
that's tutorial 6 and there's also
成立图形公司
1965年国际比赛，这是JC
that's tutorial 6 and there's also
counter folds like this piece right in
1968年的Chitty Bang Bang，这是
真的很棒的传播美丽的车
counter folds like this piece right in
the back here is counter fold
这基本上都是用盒子做的
机制，这是教程14，如果您
the back here is counter fold
that's tutorial 22 all held together
看着它结束，你会看到有一个
整体下方的支柱
that's tutorial 22 all held together
with slots less tutorial 11 highly
东西打开，然后有平行折叠
创建这个你知道在后面
with slots less tutorial 11 highly
complicated bit of pop-up design but
平行折叠教程六，然后
这些实际上是V Falls教程二
complicated bit of pop-up design but
really amazing spreads now we just have
内置到由
汽车，所以我只是认为
really amazing spreads now we just have
a look at capacitors fairy stories there
美丽真的传播了纸
接下来的三个工程师
a look at capacitors fairy stories there
are literally dozens of these this is
我给你看的书都是
保罗·泰勒（Paul Taylor）
are literally dozens of these this is
sleeping beauty from 1961 all the
我想告诉你这是
基本上是v折教程2，这是
sleeping beauty from 1961 all the
mechanisms in all these books are
拱门教程34这样
这个盒子的盖子就是
mechanisms in all these books are
counter fold tutorial 22 they usually
45度折叠，这是教程23
实际上在下面有一个支柱
counter fold tutorial 22 they usually
have some interesting little
与其中之一平行
推动盒子顶部向上的侧面
have some interesting little
moving parts are very very simple so
使它绝对方形
当然这只是一个
moving parts are very very simple so
here we have the the Prince turns into
将这两个和
下本书，这也是保罗设计的
here we have the the Prince turns into
the witch and if we open it up that same
泰勒，这是博士。杜利特尔（Doolittle），1969年
我想给你看的第一读
the witch and if we open it up that same
thing we've got these windows or empty
后面的这个是M吗
折
thing we've got these windows or empty
and by pulling that strip we get these
那是教程19提高平行四边形
这里
and by pulling that strip we get these
three Grace's or whatever they are it's
这是教程5鱼，这是一条
v折教程以及背面
three Grace's or whatever they are it's
all counter fold so when the page is
鱼这是由
V折和平行折是教程
all counter fold so when the page is
flat everything else goes flat they're
6个和两个都增加了折痕
也是在这里添加
flat everything else goes flat they're
all cut out of one piece of card if you
折痕，因此这两个教程7和
所以有点方形和笨拙，但我
all cut out of one piece of card if you
look at it end on you'll see that the
认为我认为这是一个非常酷的功能
其实很不错不错的设计
look at it end on you'll see that the
whole thing is actually it's a
这本书的最后一个是
这个的主要部分是
whole thing is actually it's a
concertina it's just one long strip of
显然，这只粉红色的蜗牛是
曲面教程13背后的内容
concertina it's just one long strip of
cards with all these very clever counter
得到这个是M折，这是轻微的
适应我把它转过来，你可以看到，但
cards with all these very clever counter
folds cut out of them giving you
基本上是M折
教程19以及这些片段的方式
folds cut out of them giving you
ordinary parallelograms angled folds and
建在这只蜗牛上，这是
45度折线，即教程23
ordinary parallelograms angled folds and
we just run through this it's the castle
当它关闭时，您可以在这里看到这些
是45度角
we just run through this it's the castle
this has got another one you can pull
与主体垂直
蜗牛，然后这些
this has got another one you can pull
see what goes on so I like the way this
我拥有的图形国际书籍
我最喜欢的东西之一是1969年
see what goes on so I like the way this
this stained-glass window turns into an
20,000个海底联盟
由Paul Taylor和第一个设计
this stained-glass window turns into an
owl we have this which here turns into a
传播是这艘奇妙的船
基于盒机制
owl we have this which here turns into a
stained-glass window very simple bit of
教程14如果我们看它就结束了
可以看到中间有一个支柱
stained-glass window very simple bit of
pull strip and here we have another one
推高甲板，然后
这些都是通过插槽来的，所以
pull strip and here we have another one
I don't think there's anything to move
那是教程11，请关注
帆上添加了这些是两个45度
I don't think there's anything to move
on that and then this one I don't think
折叠那是教程23我只是认为
这是一个可爱的设计
on that and then this one I don't think
there's anything to move on that either
这很多船的不寻常之处
他们就一直往中间走
this there up there are these these
他们跟随脊柱很容易
制作它们的方法，这已经完成了
this there up there are these these
heads that rock well there's no pull
穿过脊柱真的
不寻常，所以它实际上是一个盒子
heads that rock well there's no pull
strip to do it you just have to do it
这下面实际上是一个平面
所以这里有三架飞机，一架
strip to do it you just have to do it
with your finger they're all nodding off
在后面的脊椎上
给你盒子，然后的方式
with your finger they're all nodding off
to sleep the very last spread is this
双方已添加启用
你要把尖的眉头放在前面
to sleep the very last spread is this
one and you can actually pull the tab
我认为下一个价差是
它非常有效，但是非常简单
one and you can actually pull the tab
and the Prince comes through the arch to
这是所有的V故障V在这里折叠
用这种方式指着他们折叠下来
and the Prince comes through the arch to
give her a case this is sleeping beauty
这些V形折叠的这种方式
他们也都在该教程中，
give her a case this is sleeping beauty
from 1961 these very early capacitors
小丑是这个不对称
V折
from 1961 these very early capacitors
had eight spreads later on they reduced
这是本教程，这是不寻常的
图形国际公司用完了
had eight spreads later on they reduced
them down to six so I'll just show you a
作为保持这块的电线
所以它给你的效果
them down to six so I'll just show you a
few others this is French version the
只是漂浮在太空中的东西
最后的传播是这个，这是我们
few others this is French version the
little train
曲折
那是教程20，这个是针对性的
little train
this is 1973 all made with counter folds
v故障
那是教程3螺旋教程
this is 1973 all made with counter folds
the same as a previous book tutorial 22
10，另一件事是这种拉力
选项卡机制为您提供Axman
every spread in this one has some really
骇人的触角
教程27全部就是枢轴
every spread in this one has some really
simple movement in it so in this one the
我要向你展示的书
教程，但如果您对
simple movement in it so in this one the
you know the Train does some interesting
弹出式历史记录这本书的艺术
弹出神奇的世界
you know the Train does some interesting
moves now this is a really good one as
三维书，这是
商业
moves now this is a really good one as
you pull these little mice we get some
如果我们去这里，你会看到它已经
你可以拉一个非常棒的时间表
you pull these little mice we get some
fun
可以看到弹出窗口的方式
从一开始就发展起来
fun
plastic action there drumming again the
如果你是手风琴全部回来
对弹出式历史记录或其他感兴趣
plastic action there drumming again the
actual mechanism is really really simple
造纸工程师这是你的书
也有关于其他的各种东西
actual mechanism is really really simple
and so you actually have to hold it
造纸工程师很多现代的东西
历史涵盖了很多
and so you actually have to hold it
right or it starts going wrong but yeah
真的很棒的书
很棒的信息，只是一个可爱的
right or it starts going wrong but yeah
I just think that's delightful the way
这本书我不能推荐得足够高
[音乐]
I just think that's delightful the way
he drums and the next spread this one
[音乐]
您
he drums and the next spread this one
yeah there's nothing to actually move